techeblog.com 2019-08-20

# Privacy Policy – TechEBlog

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

We do not have access to, nor control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used.

For example, we use Google to serve advertisements on TechEBlog.com, which use the Google Doubleclick cookie, and in some cases, a unique device identifier, to show you ads based on your visit to TechEBlog.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Google Doubleclick cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit [this page](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) or [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#). You may download the AppChoices app [here](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) to opt out in mobile apps.

## Other

This site contains links to other sites. TechEBlog.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We do not collect any other personal or identifiable information through any means on our website. As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
